ketubanjiwa.com 2019-03-15

# Privacy Statement | Ketuban Jiwa - PES Patch - FIFA Mod

****PRIVACY STATEMENT** **

By visiting or using any document or resouce contained on this website – hereafter to be read as “ **www.ketubanjiwa.com** ” – you agree to be bound by the provisions of these Privacy & User Policies. If at any time you have questions or concerns regarding the information provided by this document, please forward all such discourse to **[Contact Us](https://www.ketubanjiwa.com/contact-us) Page** where the appropriate administrator will respond to you as quickly as possible.  **www.ketubanjiwa.com** reserves the right to modify, add, or remove portions of these policies at any time; it is therefore in your best interest to review this document periodically.

*** Information We Collect**

This website is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. This website collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

*** Cookies**

To enhance your online experience we use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. We use cookies to understand Internet usage and to improve our content, offerings, and advertisements. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site, allow you to download files, post comments).

*** Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors**

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites’ privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information ( **not including** your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

*** IP Adresses**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

*** Registration to our Forums**

In order to use our forums, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as gender, location, preferences) so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site.

*** Contests and Surveys**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via contests or surveys. Participation in these surverys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name), and demographic information (age, location). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

*** Newsletter**

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.

*** Indemnity**

Although our staff is diligent in providing content that is appropriate to all ages and we screen – to the best of our ability – the content beyond all external links, ketubanjiwa.com cannot be held responsible for the privacy practices and/or age specificity of any other website we link to. By viewing ketubanjiwa.com you agree not to hold us liable for any damages that may occur by any means or for any reason to yourself or your property.

By visiting www.ketubanjiwa.com you agree for our to use cookies to improve our content, you can see about our [Privacy Statement](https://www.ketubanjiwa.com/privacy-statement)
